<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2025-11-09T21:07:09+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Subnovel</title><subtitle>A web novel translation project.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Chapter 194: Choosing a Handsome Face</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2025/11/09/chapter-194.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Chapter 194: Choosing a Handsome Face" /><published>2025-11-09T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-11-09T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2025/11/09/chapter-194</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2025/11/09/chapter-194.html"><![CDATA[<p>Translator: FenrirTL
Editor/Quality Checker: Saphartlantis
Murim Term Consultant: Kopke</p>

<p>========================</p>

<p>&lt; Chapter 194: Choosing a Handsome Face &gt;</p>

<p>“Heeya, you shouldn’t move yet.”</p>

<p>Mrs. Shim held her daughter Heeya’s hand.</p>

<p>Heeya, who was getting dressed, had a face and body covered in wounds. The girl had experienced the greatest misfortune of her life. Three days ago, on her way to work, she was brutally assaulted. She was beaten and violated by a man. 1</p>

<p>“Mom, you heard him too, right? He said he’d kill us all if he’s released!”</p>

<p>The one who committed the unspeakable act against her was a man named Kongpae, a member of the Beast Sect that dominated the area. He was so brazen that he committed the atrocity in the morning, not even at night.</p>

<p>Heeya, with her broken body, personally reported the incident to the local branch of the Murim Alliance. But less than three days after Kongpae was arrested, she heard the news that he had been released. It was said that even while being dragged to the branch, he loudly proclaimed his innocence and openly threatened to harm Heeya and her family once he got out. And yet, the branch released such a man. 2</p>

<p>“Mom, we have to leave.”</p>

<p>Heeya tried to stand up, but dizziness overcame her, and she collapsed back down. There wasn’t a part of her body that didn’t hurt.</p>

<p>“Where do you think you’re going in your condition?”</p>

<p>“We have to go. He said he’d kill us!”</p>

<p>Tears welled up in Heeya’s eyes. She never imagined that they would release him so easily. What are we supposed to do? What are we supposed to do now!</p>

<p>Mrs. Shim hugged her daughter tightly.</p>

<p>“It’s all my fault. It’s because of me.”</p>

<p>She had raised her two children alone after losing her husband. She had lived a hard life, but a year ago, she had a bad fall and seriously injured her leg.</p>

<p>Unable to work, her barely ten-year-old son started working as a waiter, and her fifteen-year-old daughter Heeya, who had been helping her mother at a textile shop, took on an additional job washing dishes at an inn at night.</p>

<p>These were such good children trying to earn money for living expenses and their mother’s medicine. And yet, such misfortune had befallen her daughter.</p>

<p>Tears streamed down Mrs. Shim’s face. She gritted her teeth to avoid crying in front of her daughter, but the tears came of their own accord.</p>

<p>Heeya gritted her teeth and stood up again.</p>

<p>“Mom, pack our things. I’ll bring the cart.”</p>

<p>Mrs. Shim pulled her back.</p>

<p>“You go. Take your brother and hide somewhere for now.”</p>

<p>“Mom, we don’t have time for this. You know I won’t leave without you.”</p>

<p>“Where will you go with me? Just hide yourself for a while, okay?”</p>

<p>Heeya’s mind was filled with countless thoughts.</p>

<p>Where could she go with her sick mother and young sibling? Or should she just accept it as being bitten by a mad dog and beg for forgiveness if that person ever showed up? She couldn’t decide what the right choice was.</p>

<p>‘Someone, please tell me what to do! Please, help me!’</p>

<p>At fifteen, she had no one to cling to but the heavens. 3</p>

<p>Just then, her younger brother, Seok, opened the door and walked in.</p>

<p>“Mom! Sister!”</p>

<p>Seok looked flustered, as if something was wrong.</p>

<p>Seeing her brother, Heeya snapped to attention. She thought that leaving was the only way to save him.</p>

<p>“Pack your things, Seok.”</p>

<p>“Why should I pack?”</p>

<p>“We’re leaving. Just pack the essentials.”</p>

<p>“Sister! Wait! Listen to me first. I asked a warrior for help. He said he’d help us.”</p>

<p>Heeya and her mother, Mrs. Shim, were both stunned by his words.</p>

<p>“Who is it? Do you know him?”</p>

<p>“No. I just met him today.”</p>

<p>Hearing that it was a stranger, Heeya sighed.</p>

<p>“Seok, listen to your sister. You shouldn’t ask just anyone for help. What if that warrior gets killed by people from the Beast Sect?”</p>

<p>“No, he really looked terrifying and strong.”</p>

<p>Heeya let out another sigh.</p>

<p>“Then where is he? Why did he come alone?”</p>

<p>“He told me to go first.”</p>

<p>“He’s not coming. He probably said that because he was annoyed by a kid like you asking for help. Just pack your things.”</p>

<p>Heeya staggered as she got up. It was hard for her to even walk, but she was determined to get her mother into a cart and leave.</p>

<p>When she opened the door to go outside, she was shocked.</p>

<p>Kongpae, looking furious, was just behind and stormed inside.</p>

<p>Heeya collapsed in fear.</p>

<p>Kongpae spoke coldly.</p>

<p>“You dared report me? Because of you, I was locked up in prison for three days.”</p>

<p>Over the past three days, the only thing she had wanted to do was kill Kongpae. In her mind, she had stabbed him with a kitchen knife, beaten him to death with a hammer, and bitten his neck off. She had killed him dozens, no, hundreds of times in her imagination.</p>

<p>But now, seeing him in person, she was so terrified that she couldn’t think of anything. Her whole body trembled, and her mind went blank. 4</p>

<p>Then, Mrs. Shim, still seated, dragged herself out of the room.</p>

<p>“Look here, I was the one who reported you. If you’re going to blame anyone, blame me.”</p>

<p>Kongpae scoffed.</p>

<p>“Instead of crawling around like a worm, why don’t you take care of yourself, huh?”</p>

<p>When he insulted her mother, Heeya screamed as if she were having a fit.</p>

<p>“Shut up! Shut up! Who do you think you are? Who are you to say that! Aaaaargh!”</p>

<p>She screamed louder because she was scared.</p>

<p>“Is this girl crazy? A good beating will set her straight.”</p>

<p>When Kongpae tried to hit her, Seok burst out of the room.</p>

<p>“Stop it! Don’t touch my sister!”</p>

<p>Seok stood in front of Heeya, shielding her.</p>

<p>Heeya pulled Seok behind her. He resisted, refusing to budge, and they ended up falling backward together.</p>

<p>“What a pathetic scene. What’s the point of living like this? Just die by my hands today. I’ll bury you all in one place.”</p>

<p>It seemed like he truly intended to kill them all, as he pulled out a dagger. The sight of the gleaming blade froze both Heeya and Seok in place.</p>

<p>“Please spare us! Please spare our family!”</p>

<p>It was at that very moment that a calm voice spoke from behind them.</p>

<p>“Aren’t those pleas something that scoundrel should be saying to you?”</p>

<p>Kongpae turned around in surprise to see Geom Mugeuk and the Fist Demon King entering.</p>

<p>At a glance, Kongpae realized these two were not ordinary warriors. Especially when he met the gaze of Dan Woo-gang, who looked at him like he was nothing but an insect, Kongpae felt every hair on his body stand on end.</p>

<p>Seok shouted joyfully.</p>

<p>“The warrior! You’re here! That warrior is here!”</p>

<p>Mrs. Shim and Heeya immediately recognized that these were the warriors Seok had mentioned earlier.</p>

<p>Kongpae also realized that the young boy had called these warriors over.</p>

<p>“Sirs, there seems to be a misunderstanding. I’m in love with this woman,” Kongpae tried to excuse himself. 5</p>

<p>Geom Mugeuk motioned for silence with a finger to his lips.</p>

<p>“You’ve lost your chance to speak in this life. You have only one word left, and even that isn’t your right.”</p>

<p>Geom Mugeuk turned to Heeya.</p>

<p>“Miss, do you want an apology from that scoundrel before he dies?”</p>

<p>Before he dies?</p>

<p>Heeya looked at Geom Mugeuk, startled. Geom Mugeuk gave her a single nod.</p>

<p>Heeya shook her head. She didn’t want to exchange words with him at all.</p>

<p>“Not even his last nonsense will be allowed.”</p>

<p>The moment Kongpae tried to open his mouth to speak, Geom Mugeuk subdued his acupoints with a swift movement, blocking his blood and energy flow. He truly didn’t give Kongpae even a single chance to say anything.</p>

<p>The Fist Demon King slowly walked over to Heeya.</p>

<p>Knowing what he was about to do, Geom Mugeuk covered Seok’s eyes and ears.</p>

<p>Dan Woo-gang stood in front of Heeya. She looked up at him and swallowed hard. She had never seen someone so terrifying in her life.</p>

<p>“Show me your fist.”</p>

<p>Startled, Heeya extended her trembling hand into a fist. The Fist Demon King’s large hand enveloped her small one. He wrapped her hand in his and extended it forward together.</p>

<p>Very slowly, they extended their united fist toward Kongpae.</p>

<p>At that moment, a look of confusion spread across Kongpae’s face as if to say, ‘What is this?’</p>

<p>Fwoooosh!</p>

<p>With a deafening sound that tore through the air!</p>

<p>Bam! Bam! Bam-bam-bam! Bam-bam-bam-bam-bam-bam!</p>

<p>Kongpae’s entire body shattered as his bones broke apart and burst. From his toes to his arms and legs, ribs and spine, shoulder bones, and neck bones—nothing was left unbroken or uncrushed.</p>

<p>‘Aaaaaaaah!’</p>

<p>It was excruciating pain he had never experienced in his life. With his acupoints sealed, he couldn’t even scream, making the agony all the worse.</p>

<p>Only after enduring all that pain did his face finally cave in with a sickening thud, and he collapsed to the ground.</p>

<p>All of this was contained in that single strike when Dan Woo-gang enveloped Heeya’s hand and thrust it forward.</p>

<p>But it didn’t end there. As if not even allowing his corpse to remain in this house, the Fist Demon King flicked his hand, and Kongpae’s body flew up into the air.</p>

<p>The Fist Demon King’s other fist struck into the air.</p>

<p>Boom! Crash!</p>

<p>It sounded like thunder from the heavens, as if divine punishment had been delivered.</p>

<p>Boom-boom-boom-boom-boom!</p>

<p>A tremendous force of martial energy swept through Kongpae’s corpse. In an instant, as if by magic, Kongpae’s body vanished into thin air.</p>

<p>“Aah!”</p>

<p>Heeya couldn’t believe what she was seeing. It felt like she was witnessing a hallucination.</p>

<p>Then, Dan Woo-gang’s hand tightened once more around her fist.</p>

<p>At that moment, Heeya felt something in the fist that held hers.</p>

<p>Keep living with strength.</p>

<p>Heeya looked up at the Fist Demon King. He gazed down at her with an unreadable face.</p>

<p>She no longer found his face frightening. He didn’t seem like a demon but rather like one of the Four Heavenly Kings standing guard at a temple gate. He felt like a guardian deity protecting her from evil spirits. 6</p>

<p>Seok hadn’t seen Kongpae disintegrate into dust, but he could feel it. He knew Kongpae was dead.</p>

<p>Geom Mugeuk felt Seok’s tears trickling down his palm.</p>

<p>After lifting his hand from Seok’s eyes, Geom Mugeuk turned the boy to face him.</p>

<p>“If you keep living with the same courage you showed today, you’ll be just fine.”</p>

<p>The bravery it took for Seok to approach the terrifying Fist Demon King and ask for help—if he had that kind of courage, he would surely live well.</p>

<p>“Yes.”</p>

<p>Seok hugged Geom Mugeuk. The child trembled in his embrace, and Geom Mugeuk gently patted his head.</p>

<p>“Please, accept my bow of gratitude.”</p>

<p>Heeya tried to bow to Dan Woo-gang, but an unseen force stopped her from doing so.</p>

<p>“That’s not necessary.”</p>

<p>“Please, accept my bow. It’s the only thing I can offer.”</p>

<p>“I merely granted your brother’s request.”</p>

<p>With those words, the Fist Demon King clasped his hands behind his back and looked up at the sky.</p>

<p>Heeya looked at Seok. He ran to her and hugged her tightly.</p>

<p>“Sister.”</p>

<p>“Seok.”</p>

<p>Now, with Seok nestled in his sister’s arms, he looked over at the Fist Demon King. Although the child’s gaze was filled with admiration, respect, and gratitude, the Fist Demon King simply kept his hands behind his back, looking up at the sky. 7</p>

<p>Mrs. Shim expressed her gratitude through her tears.</p>

<p>“Thank you. I will never forget this kindness, not even in death.”</p>

<p>Geom Mugeuk spoke to Mrs. Shim and Heeya.</p>

<p>“We know this man was part of a gang. We’ll take care of everything, so you don’t have to worry about further retaliation from them anymore.”</p>

<p>But the good fortune bestowed upon this family didn’t end there.</p>

<p>Perhaps moved by a desire to extend his kindness to the very end, the Fist Demon King suddenly approached Mrs. Shim and asked abruptly.</p>

<p>“Since when?”</p>

<p>“Pardon?”</p>

<p>“Your legs. How long have they been hurting?”</p>

<p>“Oh, it’s been about a year.”</p>

<p>“May I take a look?”</p>

<p>Before the bewildered Mrs. Shim could respond, Heeya quickly spoke up.</p>

<p>“Please, we beg you!”</p>

<p>Dan Woo-gang examined Mrs. Shim’s legs.</p>

<p>“It might hurt, so please bear with it.”</p>

<p>Before she could say anything.</p>

<p>Crack. Pop. Crackle.</p>

<p>The sound of bones realigning filled the air. As the long-stiffened bones shifted, Mrs. Shim screamed in pain. But the pain didn’t last long. The Fist Demon King, with his superior knowledge of human bones and muscles, surpassed even the Demon Doctor in this expertise.</p>

<p>Moments later, surprising words came from the Fist Demon King.</p>

<p>“With some rest and care, you should be able to get up and walk again.”</p>

<p>Mrs. Shim was so stunned that she couldn’t close her mouth, and Heeya and Seok shouted with joy.</p>

<p>“Thank you, benefactor.”</p>

<p>“Thank you so much. Thank you.”</p>

<p>The three of them clung to each other, crying tears of gratitude.</p>

<p>Finally, Geom Mugeuk handed Heeya an envelope. Inside was enough money for the three of them to start a small shop and make a living.</p>

<p>Heeya, surprised, asked in a trembling voice.</p>

<p>“Why are you giving this to us?”</p>

<p>“It’s not from me. It’s money we’ll collect from that gang of his, so don’t worry and take it.”</p>

<p>How could this money, how could Kongpae’s death, ever heal her deep wounds?</p>

<p>This incident would haunt her for the rest of her life. She would have nightmares, and her distrust of men would only grow. She might even have trouble finding a partner.</p>

<p>But this was as far as Geom Mugeuk could help. “I hope you overcome this and live the rest of your life well.”</p>

<p>“Why are you showing us such great kindness?”</p>

<p>Heeya felt like she was receiving all the blessings she had never gotten in her life all at once. It seemed almost too much to be true.</p>

<p>Geom Mugeuk glanced at the Fist Demon King and said, “It’s because your brother chose the handsome face over there.”</p>

<hr />

<p>After leaving Mrs. Shim’s residence, we headed straight for the Beast Sect.</p>

<p>If we didn’t clean up after ourselves, Seok’s family would eventually face danger.</p>

<p>Before going, we found out that the Beast Sect was involved in all sorts of vile deeds. They terrorized and threatened the residents, extorted money, beat people, and even killed. They were truly the dark rulers of this area, acting like kings.</p>

<p>Though such behavior was expected from those scoundrels, the real issue was with the Murim Alliance branch that allowed it to happen.</p>

<p>“That martial arts technique you used earlier was really impressive.”</p>

<p>In truth, it was far too refined a move to waste on a lowlife like Kongpae.</p>

<p>Nevertheless, Dan Woo-gang killed him personally because of Seok. Since Seok had asked the Fist Demon King for help, he had been the one to deliver the final blow. It was to instill in Seok the pride that he had saved his family through his own choice.</p>

<p>However, what moved me more was the sight of the Fist Demon King holding Heeya’s hand and sending that scoundrel flying. I believe that, thanks to the hand the Fist Demon King held, the girl will live well. In tough times, she’ll remember those large, strong hands, and the warmth they carried.</p>

<p>“I admire you.”</p>

<p>“All you do is flatter whenever you open your mouth.”</p>

<p>“It’s sincere, Master.”</p>

<p>I subtly addressed him as ‘Master,’ but he remained as unyielding as ever.</p>

<p>“It was a good attempt, Young Master.”</p>

<p>Soon, we arrived at the mansion where the Beast Sect resided.</p>

<p>The guard at the gate, upon seeing the Fist Demon King, panicked, slammed the gate shut, and ran inside.</p>

<p>“Emergency! Emergency!”</p>

<p>Hearing the guard’s shouts, the Fist Demon King remarked wryly, “Did you see that? Just my face alone is enough to cause a state of emergency.” 8</p>

<p>If Seo Daeryong had been here, he would have teased Dan Woo-gang about it for days, but as long as the Fist Demon King was with me, I wouldn’t let his appearance bother him.</p>

<p>“I saw it. The look of admiration in that girl’s eyes as she gazed up at you.”</p>

<p>Perhaps that comment lifted his spirits.</p>

<p>The Fist Demon King placed his palm on the gate, and with a resounding crash, the heavy gate tore apart like paper.</p>

<p>Dan Woo-gang was the first to step inside. From behind, his massive back seemed to fill the entire entrance.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Translator: FenrirTL Editor/Quality Checker: Saphartlantis Murim Term Consultant: Kopke]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Chapter 195: A Gangster Reflecting Regretfully</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2025/11/09/chapter-195.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Chapter 195: A Gangster Reflecting Regretfully" /><published>2025-11-09T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-11-09T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2025/11/09/chapter-195</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2025/11/09/chapter-195.html"><![CDATA[<p>Translator: FenrirTL
Editor/Quality Checker: Saphartlantis
Murim Term Consultant: Kopke</p>

<p>========================</p>

<p>&lt; Chapter 195: A Gangster Reflecting Regretfully? &gt;</p>

<p>The leader of the Beast Sect, Gu Yasu, was watching his subordinates count the money. It was silver collected from the marketplace as tributes.</p>

<p>“Three hundred nyang.”</p>

<p>One of his men brought over a hefty pouch of money.</p>

<p>“We’re going broke because of one damn idiot. Where’s that bastard Kongpae now?”</p>

<p>In response, Yang, his right-hand man standing beside him, answered.</p>

<p>“He was released from the Murim Alliance’s branch and is probably out somewhere drinking.”</p>

<p>“When he comes in, tell him to come straight to me.”</p>

<p>“Yes, sir.”</p>

<p>The three hundred nyang was a bribe for the Murim Alliance’s branch leader. Even though he received regular payments every month, he should’ve let it slide, but he demanded three hundred nyang in exchange for releasing Kongpae.</p>

<p>But Gu Yasu couldn’t just leave Kongpae rotting in prison either. Kongpae was essential to the Beast Sect. With scumbags like him around, merchants would get scared and obediently pay up.</p>

<p>“What about the woman who reported him? She didn’t run off, did she?”</p>

<p>“Her mother is sick, so she won’t be able to run away.”</p>

<p>“Didn’t you say she was pretty? Makes sense. That’s why that horny bastard Kongpae acted up. Once things settle down, sell her off to a brothel far away. We need to at least recover half of the money lost because of her.” 1</p>

<p>“Understood.”</p>

<p>“And make sure that idiot Kongpae doesn’t touch her anymore.”</p>

<p>“Got it. By the way, the Jangdo Sect has encroached on our territory again.”</p>

<p>“Those bastards!”</p>

<p>The Jangdo Sect was a rival black-market gang from a nearby region. They often clashed whenever territorial disputes arose.</p>

<p>“There’s a rumor that they’ve recruited a martial expert.”</p>

<p>“What kind of expert?”</p>

<p>“I’m not sure. It’s said that the expert’s identity is unknown, but it seems they’re acting bold because of him.”</p>

<p>Gu Yasu snorted dismissively. Just then, one of his subordinates rushed in urgently to report.</p>

<p>“Intruders are here!”</p>

<p>At the mention of intruders, Gu Yasu immediately called for someone.</p>

<p>“Fetch Chun Mu-in.”</p>

<p>The reason Gu Yasu could dismissively snort at the Jangdo Sect recruiting a new expert was because of Chun, a master known only to Gu Yasu. The secret Gu Yasu kept was that Chun was a former member of the Demonic Cult.</p>

<p>A martial master from the Demonic Cult, Chun!</p>

<p>It was thanks to him that the Beast Sect had grown this strong.</p>

<p>When Gu Yasu and Yang stepped outside, the intruders were crossing the training grounds, walking toward them.</p>

<p>As Gu Yasu saw the figures approaching from a distance, he was taken aback.</p>

<p>“What the hell?”</p>

<p>There were two intruders: a burly, muscular man and a slender young man. Their leisurely pace made them seem more like visitors than intruders. Of course, they were Geom Mugeuk and Dan Woo-gang.</p>

<p>Yang quickly spoke up.</p>

<p>“They seem to be the ones sent by the Jangdo Sect.”</p>

<p>“The expert they supposedly recruited this time?”</p>

<p>“Yes. Who else could it be if not them?”</p>

<p>Gu Yasu nodded. There was no one else in the area who would dare to attack them other than the Jangdo Sect.</p>

<p>“Where’s Chun Mu-in?”</p>

<p>“He’ll be out soon.”</p>

<p>Around twenty members of the Beast Sect sprang from all directions, brandishing their weapons as they surrounded the two intruders.</p>

<p>“Where are you from?”</p>

<p>At Gu Yasu’s question, Geom Mugeuk glanced around and replied.</p>

<p>“You’ve turned the outside into a hellhole, but here you’re living quite comfortably.”</p>

<p>The Beast Sect’s headquarters was a newly built estate. The building Gu Yasu resided in was especially lavish, constructed with expensive materials without any reservations.</p>

<p>“I asked, who are you?”</p>

<p>To kill or to submit—ordinarily, Gu Yasu would have already barked his commands. But today, the words wouldn’t leave his lips.</p>

<p>It was because of the muscular man standing next to the young man. Gu Yasu, who had experienced all sorts of scoundrels in the underworld, had never seen anyone as terrifying as this.</p>

<p>Geom Mugeuk addressed Gu Yasu.</p>

<p>“Do you know why you keep asking who we are instead of why we’re here? It’s because you’re in the habit of first deciding whether someone’s worth killing or not.”</p>

<p>With that, Geom Mugeuk began striding directly toward Gu Yasu.</p>

<p>Startled, Gu Yasu shouted to his men.</p>

<p>“Kill him!”</p>

<p>The Beast Sect members charged at Geom Mugeuk.</p>

<p>Geom Mugeuk dodged the incoming attacks and began throwing punches.</p>

<p>To Gu Yasu, the attacks didn’t look powerful at all. Just light taps—one after another.</p>

<p>He dodged skillfully, avoiding the attacks coming from all directions while landing single blows here and there. Some men were struck in the face, others in the stomach.</p>

<p>Though Geom Mugeuk’s moves were fast, his attacks seemed devoid of any real power, which gave Gu Yasu a sense of relief.</p>

<p>‘It’s nothing special!’</p>

<p>That was exactly what he thought. In fact, he started to worry more about the muscular man standing aside, not getting involved in the fight.</p>

<p>“Get up! Get up and join forces! Stab him in the back!”</p>

<p>But the subordinates who had been struck and fallen didn’t get back up.</p>

<p>“Stop pretending and get up! You useless idiots!”</p>

<p>Gu Yasu understood, though. Even he might have pretended to be knocked out if it meant avoiding a fight with that muscular guy.</p>

<p>“Ah, I trusted these fools.”</p>

<p>In the meantime, all twenty of those who had stepped forward were down.</p>

<p>Yang kicked a fallen subordinate nearby, trying to wake him up. Geom Mugeuk just let him do as he pleased.</p>

<p>“If you don’t want to die, get up!”</p>

<p>It was obvious that the men were only pretending to be unconscious after receiving such light taps. Anyone could see it was an act.</p>

<p>Even after being kicked, they didn’t move. Yang, feeling something was off, carefully examined the fallen subordinates.</p>

<p>Yang flinched. The subordinate was dead. He checked another who had collapsed nearby; he was dead too. Yang realized then that all of the subordinates were dead.</p>

<p>Yang slowly looked up at Geom Mugeuk.</p>

<p>At that moment, his eyes met Geom Mugeuk’s. The gaze was cold and chilling, devoid of any emotion.</p>

<p>‘A true master!’</p>

<p>Yang realized that one wrong word could lead to his death on the spot.</p>

<p>Geom Mugeuk had shown no mercy in his actions. It was to ensure that no one survived to seek revenge and harm Seok’s family.</p>

<p>Just then, Chun appeared. His hair was disheveled, likely from drinking too much the previous night, and his unshaven face made him look incredibly haggard. He also had gained quite a bit of weight since joining the Beast Sect. Still, Gu Yasu didn’t mind; Chun had never failed to eliminate a target so far.</p>

<p>“Get rid of both of them.”</p>

<p>Chun walked forward with long strides, paying no attention to the fallen members of the Beast Sect. He knew their skills were mediocre.</p>

<p>He was, after all, a former member of the Eastern Fist Faction, specifically from the Iron Fist branch. Though he had reached the rank of Blue Fist, he eventually fled to the Demonic Cult, unable to endure the grueling training. 2</p>

<p>Since then, Chun had been hiding within the Beast Sect. Many had tried to target Gu Yasu, but they all died at Chun’s hands. In return, he received ample money to indulge in his vices. In this third-rate underworld, even the abilities of a Blue Fist practitioner were sufficient for Chun to reign as a Fist Demon King.</p>

<p><em>Whoosh.</em></p>

<p>Chun’s fist, aimed at smashing Geom Mugeuk’s head, halted in mid-air.</p>

<p>The problem wasn’t that Geom Mugeuk had effortlessly dodged his attack; it was what Geom Mugeuk said next.</p>

<p>“This is Blue Fist martial arts, isn’t it?”</p>

<p>Chun was startled. It was the first time anyone had recognized his martial arts.</p>

<p>Right then, Chun’s eyes finally settled on a figure standing with his back turned, gazing at the sky—the massive man who now turned his head towards him.</p>

<p>The moment he saw that face!</p>

<p>“Aaargh!”</p>

<p>Chun let out a scream. He was so shocked it felt like his heart would burst. The hangover that had plagued him all day vanished instantly.</p>

<p>Gu Yasu, who was behind Chun, couldn’t see his face, but Yang could.</p>

<p>He saw Chun’s twisted expression. It was hard to believe that such profound despair and fear could manifest on a human face.</p>

<p>The Fist Demon King muttered under his breath, almost to himself.</p>

<p>“You used my martial arts to serve as the lackey of some black-market thug?”</p>

<p>The Fist Demon King’s words carried no emotion. The moment he finished speaking—</p>

<p><em>Thud! Crack!</em></p>

<p>Chun immediately struck his own celestial acupoint and took his life. He knew there was no escape, no forgiveness. If he were to die at the hands of the Fist Demon King, his death would be far more painful. 3</p>

<p>Seeing this, Gu Yasu’s mind went blank. The situation was so bizarre that he found himself unable to think.</p>

<p>As Geom Mugeuk walked past Yang, he spoke.</p>

<p>“Follow me.”</p>

<p>“Yes!”</p>

<p>Yang obediently followed the order as if Geom Mugeuk were naturally his leader all along.</p>

<p>Gu Yasu snapped back to his senses when Geom Mugeuk approached him. Now, there was only one thing he could rely on.</p>

<p>“Do you know who’s behind us? If you mess with us, there will be consequences.”</p>

<p>“Who’s behind you?”</p>

<p>“The Murim Alliance.”</p>

<p>“The entire Murim Alliance belongs to you?”</p>

<p>“The head of this branch supports me. If you touch me, he won’t stand still.”</p>

<p>Geom Mugeuk turned to Yang.</p>

<p>“Can you bring the branch leader here?”</p>

<p>Yang hesitated, realizing it wouldn’t be easy.</p>

<p>“If you bring him here, you’ll be the leader of the Beast Sect.”</p>

<p>“I’ll bring him no matter what it takes.”</p>

<p>Gu Yasu glared at Yang as if he wanted to kill him as he ran out without hesitation.</p>

<p>“That damned bastard.”</p>

<p>He didn’t expect Yang to betray him so easily. After all, Yang was his right-hand man for many years.</p>

<p>Once Yang left, Geom Mugeuk spoke.</p>

<p>“There’s no need to be so angry. The promise to make him the leader was a lie.”</p>

<p>Gu Yasu’s expression relaxed slightly at that moment.</p>

<p>“It’s not like you’ve been in the dark side for just a day or two; you know everyone dies, right?”</p>

<p>Gu Yasu’s face hardened again. He realized that Geom Mugeuk’s words included him too.</p>

<p>“Please, spare me.”</p>

<p>Geom Mugeuk said to him, “Give me evidence of the bribes you gave to the branch leader.”</p>

<p>Gu Yasu’s eyes darted around.</p>

<p>“If you don’t have it, just die.”</p>

<p>As Geom Mugeuk clenched his fist, Gu Yasu shouted.</p>

<p>“I have it! It’s in the safe.”</p>

<p>Geom Mugeuk led him to the safe. Gu Yasu’s hands trembled as he opened it. The fear came rushing in, as he belatedly realized the gravity of the situation. Chun’s suicide, someone he trusted deeply to reslove problems, weighed heavily on him.</p>

<p>“Here it is.”</p>

<p>He pulled out a ledger from the safe. It contained details of the bribes given to the Murim Alliance branch leader and records of all the corruption he had committed.</p>

<p>“Go and move the bodies where they can’t be seen.”</p>

<p>Gu Yasu walked toward the corpses.</p>

<p>‘This is my chance!’</p>

<p>Gu Yasu made up his mind to seize the opportunity and escape, but before he knew it, his inner energy at his dantian had been suppressed, leaving him unable to use it.</p>

<p>‘When did this even happen?’</p>

<p>With no other choice, Gu Yasu went ahead and cleared the corpses. Without his inner energy, moving about twenty bodies left him drenched in sweat. Having lived his whole life without lifting a finger, this felt like torture.</p>

<p>After laboriously clearing all the corpses, Gu Yasu returned to Geom Mugeuk.</p>

<p>“They’re all cleared.”</p>

<p>“Exhausted? Feeling powerless?”</p>

<p>“…Yes.”</p>

<p>“The people who suffered at your hands felt that a hundred or a thousand times more than this. As individual pieces, you’re insignificant, but like a pack of dogs, you roamed together, intimidating, robbing, beating, and killing.”</p>

<p>“From now on, I’ll turn over a new leaf.” 4</p>

<p>“A man of the underworld, talking about repentance? How unsophisticated. Keep doing bad things, but do them where I tell you. There’ll be plenty of partners there, so you’ll be fine.”</p>

<p>“Where is that?”</p>

<p>“Hell.”</p>

<p>Geom Mugeuk’s fist flew at him.</p>

<p>Second Technique: Thunderous Asura Fist.</p>

<p><em>Thud! Thud! Thud! Thud! Thud!</em></p>

<p>In a flash, dozens of punches landed on him like lightning strikes, and without a chance to scream, he died a bloody mess.</p>

<p>Geom Mugeuk dumped his body unceremoniously into the warehouse with the other corpses. He gave no significance to the man’s death.</p>

<p>A short while later, the Murim Alliance Branch Leader, Baekchul, arrived at the scene.</p>

<p>“Why does it smell like blood in here? Didn’t I tell you bastards to stop killing people?”</p>

<p>Baekchul grumbled at Yang as he stepped inside. He had visited so frequently that he felt at home there.</p>

<p>“What’s so important that you dragged a busy man like me all the way here?”</p>

<p>Baekchul flinched when he saw Geom Mugeuk and the Fist Demon King.</p>

<p>“Who are they?”</p>

<p>“They’re new warriors we recruited.”</p>

<p>Baekchul looked surprised at Yang’s calm response.</p>

<p>“Where did you find guys that big? Just having them stand around is worth their meals. But where’s your boss?”</p>

<p>Yang answered nonchalantly, “Seems he stepped out for a moment.”</p>

<p>At that moment, Geom Mugeuk spoke to Baekchul.</p>

<p>“How could you just let someone go after assaulting and raping a young girl?”</p>

<p>Baekchul turned to Yang with a look that said, ‘What’s going on here?’ Didn’t these new guys know who he was? Hadn’t they been properly briefed?</p>

<p>But Yang just stood there, observing the situation silently. Baekchul sensed that something was wrong from Yang’s uncharacteristic reaction.</p>

<p>Baekchul responded calmly, “Ah, that case? We let him go due to lack of evidence.”</p>

<p>“The girl’s whole body was battered, and the thug was bragging about it to his fellow underworld scum. What do you mean, lack of evidence? You didn’t even investigate, did you?”</p>

<p>Baekchul was inwardly seething with anger, but given the atmosphere, he couldn’t retort.</p>

<p>“If it were your family, would you have just let it slide?”</p>

<p>Mentioning his family made Baekchul’s expression instantly harden.</p>

<p>“You really think you can get away with this?”</p>

<p>“Feeling upset because I brought up your family? Your family is so precious, but do you think other people’s families deserve to suffer?” 5</p>

<p>In that moment, Baekchul considered drawing his sword but held back for now.</p>

<p>‘I’ll make sure they all pay later.’</p>

<p>Getting out of this situation was the priority. Baekchul forced a smile and spoke in a conciliatory tone.</p>

<p>“Please understand. The main alliance has its laws, you know.”</p>

<p>“Whose laws are those for? You? The Beast Sect? Who, exactly?”</p>

<p>Baekchul took a step back under the chill of Geom Mugeuk’s overwhelming presence.</p>

<p>“I don’t know who you are, but I am the branch leader of the Murim Alliance. Touching me makes you an enemy of the martial world!”</p>

<p>“That won’t happen. I know someone in the Murim Alliance, and I’ll make sure your crimes and everything about this place are reported.”</p>

<p>“To whom?”</p>

<p>“There’s someone high up there, the person who once wanted to make me their son-in-law.”</p>

<p>Baekchul thought this was nonsense, but he held his tongue.</p>

<p>“My crimes? Do you have evidence?”</p>

<p>Geom Mugeuk pulled out the ledger he had taken from the Beast Sect.</p>

<p>“You’ve pocketed a lot of bribes from the Beast Sect. You even used them to kill people for your own interests.”</p>

<p>“What nonsense is this? I’ve never done such a thing.”</p>

<p>“You think denying it will change anything? They’ve meticulously recorded everything.”</p>

<p>Baekchul’s face stiffened.</p>

<p>“They’re framing me!”</p>

<p>“That’s not true. They weren’t in a position to lie.”</p>

<p>Baekchul knew he needed to get that ledger at any cost. Taking care of them would come next.</p>

<p>“How much? How much for that ledger…?”</p>

<p><em>Whooosh.</em></p>

<p><em>Bang!</em></p>

<p>Baekchul disappeared before their eyes.</p>

<p>Far away, Baekchul was smashed against the exterior wall, his body shattered, and he died instantly.</p>

<p>Now left alone, Yang looked around cautiously and said,</p>

<p>“Then from now on, I’ll be the leader of the Beast Sect…”</p>

<p><em>Whooosh!</em></p>

<p><em>Bang!</em></p>

<p>Yang also vanished from sight.</p>

<p>He was sent flying in the opposite direction, ending up a bloody mess too.</p>

<p>The one who sent both of them flying was Dan Woo-gang. With a single punch, he had sent them to the afterlife.</p>

<p>“Let’s go.”</p>

<p>His eyes seemed to say, ‘Why bother talking with scum like these?’</p>

<p>“I was thinking of asking for about a million nyang for the ledger.”</p>

<p>“Stop joking around.”</p>

<p>“Just a moment.”</p>

<p>Geom Mugeuk carefully buried the ledger inside a box in a corner of the courtyard.</p>

<p>After burying the ledger, Geom Mugeuk planned to inform the investigator sent by the Alliance Leader so that it would be handled properly. He also intended not to forget to include a message in the letter, asking them to take good care of Seok’s family.</p>

<p>Watching Geom Mugeuk, the Fist Demon King commented, “You’re very meticulous.”</p>

<p>“When helping others, you have to be thorough. It’s nice to help others, but if you don’t finish properly just because it’s bothersome, the one who ends up suffering is the person you helped. I get the satisfaction, but they get the consequences. That’s not right, is it?”</p>

<p>Dan Woo-gang unexpectedly replied, “I don’t think you should become the Heavenly Demon.”</p>

<p>“Why do you say that?”</p>

<p>“The Heavenly Demon has to deal with so many people. Can you endure it with a mindset like this? If you try to handle everything so meticulously, you’ll be the first to go mad.” 6</p>

<p>“Now that I think about it, you’re right. I understand. Instead of becoming the Heavenly Demon, I’ll just be your disciple, Fist Demon King.” 7</p>

<p>Dan Woo-gang quietly looked at me and then gave a faint smile.</p>

<p>“That’s the best attempt you’ve made so far.”</p>

<p>“You almost fell for it; that’s a shame.”</p>

<p>Geom Mugeuk and Dan Woo-gang walked out of the manor side by side. Just like when they entered, the Fist Demon King’s broad back filled the entrance as they exited.</p>

<p>Fortunately, the Fist Demon King didn’t mention returning to the Cult. As if asking where they should go next, Geom Mugeuk smiled at the look in his eyes and said,</p>

<p>“This time, it’s somewhere that will please you even more than it did me.”</p>

<p>1 : What trash.</p>

<p>2 : What a happy coincidence, get prepared for some heartfelt reunion ^^</p>

<p>3 : This dude sure was decisive.</p>

<p>4 : Oh please, do you think he’s Batman ? Getting put in prison to escape next week ?</p>

<p>5 : Yeah he doesn’t deserve to feel upset. His family would/should be ashamed of him.</p>

<p>6 : True, he’ll need to delegate a lot. Especially if he’ll run away frequently.</p>

<p>7 : You stretched a pole there, Fist Demon King XDXDXD</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Translator: FenrirTL Editor/Quality Checker: Saphartlantis Murim Term Consultant: Kopke]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Chapter 196: Every Time You See That Scar</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2025/11/09/chapter-196.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Chapter 196: Every Time You See That Scar" /><published>2025-11-09T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-11-09T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2025/11/09/chapter-196</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2025/11/09/chapter-196.html"><![CDATA[<p>Translator: FenrirTL
Editor/Quality Checker: Saphartlantis, Mani
Murim Term Consultant: Kopke</p>

<p>========================</p>

<p>&lt; Chapter 196: Every Time You See That Scar &gt;</p>

<p>The boat, carrying passengers, was crossing the river.</p>

<p>The Fist Demon King and I stood on the windy deck, gazing at the river. We were gradually drifting away from the Cult.</p>

<p>Some people feel uneasy about deviation. They worry—will something go wrong? Or will this incident change his life for the worse? Could it all be my fault?</p>

<p>However, I felt no unease about Dan Woo-gang’s deviation. Was it because of the sincerity he displayed in his life? Or perhaps, I thought that sincerity was suppressing his true nature.</p>

<p>It was then.</p>

<p>A soft thud echoed.</p>

<p>A ball made of yarn rolled to the Fist Demon King’s feet.</p>

<p>A young child ran up but stopped, looking scared at the towering figure of the Fist Demon King. He picked up the ball and handed it to me.</p>

<p>“Please give it to the child directly.”</p>

<p>“Do you want to make the kid cry?”</p>

<p>“He won’t cry.”</p>

<p>The Fist Demon King offered the ball to the child, but the child hesitated to approach, so he rolled the ball gently toward him.</p>

<p>Kid, today you received a ball from the Unbeatable Fist Demon.</p>

<p>The child picked up the ball, bowed, and ran back to his parents. Watching the child, Dan Woo-gang suddenly asked me a question.</p>

<p>“You said we’re going to a place where I’ll be happy?”</p>

<p>“Yes.”</p>

<p>“And how do you know what will make me happy?”</p>

<p>“Shall we make a bet?”</p>

<p>“What kind of bet?”</p>

<p>“If you enjoy yourself, I win. If not, I lose.”</p>

<p>“What if I’m happy but say I’m not?”</p>

<p>“You wouldn’t do that, would you?”</p>

<p>“If it’s a bet, we need stakes, don’t we?”</p>

<p>“We’ll bet our pride.”</p>

<p>It was the same when we jumped off the waterfall.</p>

<p>The Fist Demon King looked at me with a peculiar expression.</p>

<p>“Why are you looking at me like that?”</p>

<p>“Don’t you want to bet the Third Technique?”</p>

<p>“Of course, I do.”</p>

<p>“Then why don’t you suggest it?” 1</p>

<p>“I won the First Fist and Second Technique too easily because you showed mercy. I have some pride; I can’t do that again.”</p>

<p>It was both a sincere statement and a bid to earn his favor.</p>

<p>“Alright then, let’s bet a man’s pride!”</p>

<p>I held out my fist to him.</p>

<p>“What’s this? You want to fight?”</p>

<p>“When martial artists make a promise, they clash their weapons, don’t they? As practitioners of martial arts, we should bump fists.”</p>

<p>“I don’t clash fists with baby hands.”</p>

<p>I glanced at the Fist Demon King’s hand and then at my own fist.</p>

<p>“As much as it pains me, I can’t deny it.”</p>

<p>Dan Woo-gang turned his body towards the river.</p>

<p>In the distance, the sun began to set over the water.</p>

<p>“Not bad.”</p>

<p>It was the first time he expressed that he liked the scenery. The Fist Demon King was staring at the river, while I leaned against the railing, facing the sunset with my back to him.</p>

<p>“I heard you traveled a lot in your youth.”</p>

<p>“I wasn’t tied to the Cult.”</p>

<p>“They say you often went out with my father, too?”</p>

<p>“Did the Cult Leader tell you that?”</p>

<p>I answered quietly, “Yes,” but, in truth, it wasn’t something I heard from my father. It was information I found while investigating the Demon Supremes before my regression. The place we were heading to now was also something I discovered that way.</p>

<p>“Do you still meet Father often these days?”</p>

<p>“Hardly at all. Even at that tavern, it had been a long time since we last met.”</p>

<p>“Is everything alright?”</p>

<p>“What could be wrong? Relationships can’t always be warm, can they?”</p>

<p>“That’s true.”</p>

<p>I turned my body around. The sunset that had colored Dan Woo-gang now fell on my face.</p>

<p>Could this idle moment be remembered as one of our most intense?</p>

<hr />

<p>Two days later, Geom Mugeuk and the Fist Demon King were walking through a busy marketplace crowded with people. If the place where the Beast Sect had been previously belonged to the Murim Alliance, this area was under the control of the Unorthodox Alliance.</p>

<p>As they walked, Dan Woo-gang’s expression subtly changed. His face tightened, and at times, he showed a flash of intensity.</p>

<p>The two arrived at a shabby warehouse building on the outskirts of the area.</p>

<p>Geom Mugeuk handed some money to the person guarding the entrance. After receiving the money, the guard led them inside. There was a passage leading underground between piles of cargo.</p>

<p>After descending the stairs for a while, they reached a large iron door. As soon as it was opened, they were hit by a blast of heat and the roar of a crowd.</p>

<p>In the center was a large arena where two shirtless men were fighting each other with bare fists.</p>

<p>“This is an underground fighting arena.” 2</p>

<p>There are various types of underground arenas in the Central Plains. Some use inner power, while others employ weapons. And then there were places like this one, where the fights were pure, involving nothing but fists—no inner power, no weapons.</p>

<p>“You can just pay the entrance fee and watch the matches, or you can place bets on who the winner will be. Most people come mainly for the betting.”</p>

<p>“How did you find this place?”</p>

<p>“I have a great interest in all things related to martial arts. Since it’s a place where people fight purely with fists, I thought that you might enjoy it, so I brought you here.” 3</p>

<p>There was a tremble in the Fist Demon King’s eyes.</p>

<p>“What’s wrong? You don’t like it?”</p>

<p>Then, Dan Woo-gang said something surprising.</p>

<p>“When I was young, I used to be a fighter here.”</p>

<p>“What?”</p>

<p>Geom Mugeuk was surprised. Or rather, he pretended to be. After all, he already knew that the Fist Demon King was from this place.</p>

<p>“Here? You mean this place?”</p>

<p>“Yes, right here.”</p>

<p>Dan Woo-gang’s life had not been a smooth one, either.</p>

<p>“Then how did you end up joining the Cult?”</p>

<p>“I was scouted by someone from the Cult after they noticed me here.”</p>

<p>That part, even Geom Mugeuk didn’t know. It must have been before the Fist Demon King started learning proper martial arts, but still, with the potential he had, how could his skills go unnoticed?</p>

<p>“Were you undefeated here as well?”</p>

<p>In response to Geom Mugeuk’s question, the Fist Demon King countered.</p>

<p>“I’m not undefeated even now, am I?”</p>

<p>“What do you mean?”</p>

<p>“I couldn’t win against the Cult Leader, nor could I beat the leaders of the Murim Alliance or the Unorthodox Alliance, right? I don’t need to bring up the countless hidden masters out there. Even with you right in front of me, I can’t say for sure that I’d win.”</p>

<p>“I’m just a baby hand, remember?”</p>

<p>“That Black Demon Sword in those baby hands is quite fearsome.”</p>

<p>Geom Mugeuk suddenly thought that maybe the Fist Demon King disliked his epithet of “Undefeated.”</p>

<p>“You never know. If it came down to a real fight to the death, who knows what the outcome might be? You might even beat my father, wouldn’t you?”</p>

<p>Dan Woo-gang’s gaze returned to the arena. Watching a martial artist getting beaten within an inch of his life, he spoke.</p>

<p>“If I fought the Cult Leader, that’s what it would look like. Even if the Cult Leader didn’t draw his sword.”</p>

<p>Geom Mugeuk nodded.</p>

<p>“True. He’s the kind of person who would even beat his own child like that.”</p>

<p>At Geom Mugeuk’s words, the Fist Demon King nodded with a serious expression.</p>

<p>In truth, Geom Mugeuk didn’t know what kind of memories the Fist Demon King had of this place. Perhaps they were memories he despised, and it could very well be a place he never wanted to revisit.</p>

<p>But even so, he brought him here because the Fist Demon King had become who he was now. He had risen from the very bottom of the world of fists to its peak.</p>

<p>Wouldn’t he want to come back at least once? Wouldn’t he want to feel that intense heat once more?</p>

<p>Geom Mugeuk and the Fist Demon King stood among the crowd, watching the match.</p>

<p>The heat of this place was so intense that even with the intimidating presence of the Fist Demon King nearby, no one paid any attention to him. 3</p>

<p>Geom Mugeuk realized that these people, lost in the excitement, weren’t just absorbed in the fight—they were caught up in the gambling. They were shouting only for the outcome of the fight.</p>

<p>After watching the fight for a moment, Dan Woo-gang casually muttered.</p>

<p>“The one on the left will win.”</p>

<p>Whose judgment could be wrong here?</p>

<p>Sure enough, the fighter on the left emerged victorious.</p>

<p>The matches continued without pause. As soon as one match ended, three or four men would rush out to quickly clean the sweat and blood from the stage.</p>

<p>Meanwhile, other men displayed large boards showing the fighters’ past records and recent performance stats for the next match. People would place their bets based on these.</p>

<p>The whole process happened in a flash, as if time was money, and as if they couldn’t afford to let the audience’s excitement cool down. The matches went on relentlessly. 4</p>

<p>The Fist Demon King accurately predicted the outcome of the next match as well. He was like a prophet.</p>

<p>“We might walk out of here rich at this rate,” I joked.</p>

<p>Despite my words, I didn’t place a single bet.</p>

<p>“Why don’t you place a bet for fun?” Dan Woo-gang suggested.</p>

<p>“No, thanks.”</p>

<p>“Why not?”</p>

<p>“To be honest, I’m having second thoughts. I brought you here to feel the heat of the fights, but it seems like the heat of gambling is even stronger.”</p>

<p>At Geom Mugeuk’s frank words, the Fist Demon King gave a bitter smile.</p>

<p>“It was the same back then. This place… it’s always been like this.”</p>

<p>Dan Woo-gang suddenly fixed his gaze on a young fighter.</p>

<p>“That young fellow has a good look in his eyes.”</p>

<p>I could sense it—he was seeing his younger self in that fighter.</p>

<p>“Alright, then. I’ll bet my entire fortune on that kid,” I said jokingly.</p>

<p>The Fist Demon King encouraged me, “Go ahead. He’s bound to win.”</p>

<p>“No, I’m good.”</p>

<p>But the young fighter the Fist Demon King had predicted to win lost the match. His expression hardened slightly at the result.</p>

<p>“If I had bet as you suggested, I would’ve lost my entire fortune. We’d be sleeping on the streets tonight!” I remarked jokingly.</p>

<p>It wasn’t that the Fist Demon King had misjudged their skills. There was match-fixing involved.</p>

<p>“Should we go have a word with the owner?” I asked.</p>

<p>It would have been like the Fist Demon King to give the owner a piece of his mind.</p>

<p>“The match-fixing likely has nothing to do with the arena itself. In fact, the arena management would probably try to root it out. They make a fortune just letting things run their course; they wouldn’t bother with fixing matches and risk causing trouble.”</p>

<p>He meant that the manipulation was likely happening from the outside.</p>

<p>“Some memories are best left buried. I’m sorry,” I apologized.</p>

<p>“What do you have to be sorry about?”</p>

<p>“I brought you here hoping you’d enjoy watching the fights, but I’m worried you might just be upset now.”</p>

<p>“It’s fine,” the Fist Demon King reassured.</p>

<p>“Times have changed a lot. It seems like pure fights like the old days don’t exist anymore.”</p>

<p>Then, with a peculiar smile, Dan Woo-gang turned to me and said, “Why do you think there was no match-fixing back then?”</p>

<p>“There was?”</p>

<p>“Of course. It’s what changed my life.”</p>

<p>The Fist Demon King’s gaze shifted to the young fighter leaving the arena, and naturally, he began recalling his past.</p>

<p>“It was one of those days when I was on a winning streak. The local Black Path leader came to see me in the dead of night with his subordinates. He asked me to throw the next match. Given my winning streak, if I lost, they stood to make a lot of money. He even offered me a share—a pretty substantial amount.”</p>

<p>“What did you do?”</p>

<p>“I refused.”</p>

<p>“They wouldn’t have taken that well, I imagine.”</p>

<p>The Fist Demon King nodded and closed his eyes. The memories of that moment came back as vividly as if it were yesterday.</p>

<p>He remembered the fight, throwing punches and dodging blows from those Black Path thugs.</p>

<p>He managed to knock down all the subordinates who had come with the leader, but he couldn’t handle the leader himself. The leader had formally trained in martial arts, while he hadn’t started learning martial arts yet. In the end, the leader subdued him completely.</p>

<p>“If you don’t listen, you’ll die.”</p>

<p>“You damn Black Path bastard! If you’re a real man, fight me in the arena without using your inner power!”</p>

<p>“Talking won’t get you anywhere.”</p>

<p>The leader pulled open the Fist Demon King’s shirt.</p>

<p>Swish!</p>

<p>With a dagger, he slashed a long cut across the Fist Demon King’s chest. He clenched his teeth, trying not to scream in pain.</p>

<p>“Since you have to lose anyway, what’s a little pain, right?”</p>

<p>Eventually, the Fist Demon King couldn’t hold back and screamed in agony.</p>

<p>“Alright, I’ll lose the next match.”</p>

<p>“If you’d just said that from the start, you wouldn’t have gotten hurt. Every time you get stupid ideas, look at this scar.”</p>

<p>“It wasn’t impressive; I was just reckless and fearless back then. Even now, when I’m a thousand times stronger, I was far more fearless back then.”</p>

<p>Dan Woo-gang pulled his shirt open again, showing me the scar on his chest.</p>

<p>“This scar on my body was earned that way. It’s not from some grand master; it’s a pathetic and disgraceful mark left by some nameless Black Path thug whose name I don’t even remember. I didn’t get this fighting a Murim Alliance elder.”</p>

<p>I sensed that the Fist Demon King had probably never told anyone about this scar. It wasn’t just a scar on his body—it was a wound on his heart.</p>

<p>“Isn’t it a more honorable scar?” I asked.</p>

<p>“Honorable?”</p>

<p>“Wasn’t it far scarier than fighting a Murim Alliance elder? And yet, you endured it.”</p>

<p>“You might want to paint it in a positive light, but to me, it’s nothing but a stain I wish I could erase.”</p>

<p>“Please don’t say that. I’ve actually grown to like that scar even more. From now on, every time I see that scar, I’ll be reminded of the young Fist Demon King who stood tall without a shred of inner power. I think it’s a far more impressive scar than any blow left by the Murim Alliance Leader or any wound from the Unorthodox Alliance Leader.” 5</p>

<p>Having never thought of it that way or heard such words before, the Fist Demon King felt momentarily bewildered. He’d always felt bad when he saw the scar, but today, he thought, maybe those unpleasant feelings might lessen just a little.</p>

<p>Geom Mugeuk knew that to heal the wounds of the heart, the essential thing was the words someone else offers. No matter how much you think things over a hundred or a thousand times by yourself, it’s only when someone says something like this that the healing truly begins.</p>

<p>“Show me that scar often.”</p>

<p>The Fist Demon King, feeling a warmth stirring deep within him, was at a loss for words and simply stared at Geom Mugeuk in silence.</p>

<p>The leader laughed as he walked away.</p>

<p>After hearing the story, Geom Mugeuk asked, “So, what happened?”</p>

<p>“What do you think? I went out and won the next match decisively. I made that bastard lose his entire fortune.” 6</p>

<p>Geom Mugeuk burst into loud laughter. Yes, this was exactly like the Fist Demon King.</p>

<p>“That’s impressive!”</p>

<p>Whether he understood his thoughts or not, Geom Mugeuk asked again.</p>

<p>“Tell me the next part of the story. That Black Path thug must have come to kill you, right?”</p>

<p>The Fist Demon King nodded, recalling the day his fate had changed.</p>

<p>“That night, he came for me with all his subordinates in tow.”</p>

<p>1 : To truly obtain your loyalty, he can’t take advantage of you all the time.</p>

<p>2 : The Thunderdome !!! Two men enter, one man kill !!! Two men enter, one man die !!!</p>

<p>3 : I’m getting flashbacks from Street Cultivation. Really good books from a really good author. Try to read it ^^</p>

<p>4 : The whole principle of gambling is not letting the excitement fall, or else rationality will resurface and they will stop spending so much money.</p>

<p>5 : I agree, it’s far more difficult to be courageous when you’re powerless than when you’re one of the strongest in the world.</p>

<p>6 : Lol, get rekted XDXDXD</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Translator: FenrirTL Editor/Quality Checker: Saphartlantis, Mani Murim Term Consultant: Kopke]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Chapter 197: I Will Become the Heavenly Demon</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2025/11/09/chapter-197.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Chapter 197: I Will Become the Heavenly Demon" /><published>2025-11-09T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-11-09T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2025/11/09/chapter-197</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2025/11/09/chapter-197.html"><![CDATA[<p>Translator: FenrirTL
Editor/Quality Checker: Saphartlantis
Murim Term Consultant: Kopke</p>

<p>========================</p>

<p>&lt; Chapter 197: I Will Become the Heavenly Demon &gt;</p>

<p>The moment the match result was confirmed, Chu Ga-o, the leader of the Black Path branch, immediately mobilized his subordinates.</p>

<p>The young Fist Demon King, who was waiting at his home, was prepared for death, as he was under heavy surveillance with no way to escape. Otherwise, he wouldn’t have spoken the way he did as soon as he saw Chu Ga-o.</p>

<p>“Made a lot of money, didn’t you?”</p>

<p>Chu Ga-o’s anger surged to its peak.</p>

<p>“You won’t die peacefully.” 1</p>

<p>This time, he had suffered a massive loss. It wasn’t just his own money; he had also involved funds from other organizations, putting his own life at risk.</p>

<p>On top of that, this young fighter had twisted the knife even further.</p>

<p>“I’ve told the arena owner about this. You know who’s backing the arena, right?” 2</p>

<p>Chu Ga-o’s expression hardened. The backer, the Unorthodox Alliance, was intimidating enough that he only dared to manipulate matches discreetly during the most critical moments.</p>

<p>He had been doing fine until now, but this time, he’d made a grave mistake. He had never encountered someone this crazy before. He knew the kid had a temper, but he never imagined that even after leaving such a large scar on his chest to intimidate him, he would pull something like this.</p>

<p>“A foolish kid who doesn’t value his life.”</p>

<p>“It’s your life that’s in danger!”</p>

<p>Through this ordeal, the Fist Demon King had made a resolution: no matter what life he led, he would never have friends or family.</p>

<p>How perfect is that? It allowed him to defy such dirty threats and do as he pleased.</p>

<p>Of course, it was unfortunate. He would die here today, unable to put his resolution into practice.</p>

<p>Chu Ga-o gave orders to his subordinates.</p>

<p>“Bring that bastard to his knees in front of me.”</p>

<p>Chu Ga-o had no intention of letting this wretch die easily.</p>

<p>Dozens of Black Path men drew their weapons simultaneously. Though the Fist Demon King had been undefeated in the arena, facing such a large number without any inner power was a daunting challenge.</p>

<p>Yet the Fist Demon King remained entirely undaunted.</p>

<p>“For every one of you I kill, I’ll save another life,” he declared. 3</p>

<p>He pulled gloves from his coat and slipped them on. Sharp spikes, like awls, protruded from the front of the gloves.</p>

<p>“They’re coated with deadly poison. Even a scratch will have you lying in bed for life, sipping gruel.”</p>

<p>It was a lie. But it was a tactic to make them hesitate.</p>

<p>Among the Black Path men gathered, those who had fought the Fist Demon King before flinched. The last time they fought him, they ended up injured and knocked out—and now he was claiming his fists were laced with poison?</p>

<p>“You cowardly bastard!”</p>

<p>At Chu Ga-o’s command, Dan Woo-gang shouted back.</p>

<p>“What? You guys are running around with swords, but I can’t use these? You come at me six dozens against one and I’m not allowed to have an advantage ? You trashy Black Path bastards! Come at me, all of you!” 4</p>

<p>Chu Ga-o yelled out, “Kill him! I’ll give three hundred nyang to the one who kills him first!”</p>

<p>With a reward that outweighed everything else, the Black Path men charged at him, swinging their swords.</p>

<p>The Fist Demon King ran toward the back courtyard. The leading Black Path men, who had been chasing him enthusiastically, suddenly fell into a pit.</p>

<p>“Arghhh!”</p>

<p>The courtyard had been prepared with traps, sharp spear tips planted at the bottom.</p>

<p>The Fist Demon King had come fully prepared to fight today. He wasn’t thinking of fighting with just his fists. His goal was to survive, and if he were to die, he planned to take as many of them with him as possible.</p>

<p>A few men fell into the pit and died, but the Black Path men were seasoned fighters. Against a martial artist, they might have hesitated, but this was just a young man without any inner power.</p>

<p>Driven by greed, they relentlessly swung their swords at him. If they managed to land a sword in his body, the three hundred nyang reward would be theirs. The men, crazed by the promise of money, charged at him like madmen.</p>

<p>The Fist Demon King moved with incredible speed, dodging incoming swords and throwing punches.</p>

<p>The men who were struck by his spiked fists screamed in pain.</p>

<p>Curses filled the air, and the Black Path men were in a frenzy. They charged at him, screaming even as blood poured from their wounds.</p>

<p>Dan Woo-gang dodged blades flying at him from all directions, rolling on the ground.</p>

<p>He leaped up and dashed toward a wall, then spun around and threw a dagger. The blade embedded itself in the body of a man chasing him. He threw stones from the ground, picked up the enemies’ swords, and swung them around.</p>

<p>Chu Ga-o shouted, “You’ve betrayed the honor of a fighter!”</p>

<p>It was a taunt meant to keep him from using other weapons, but it had no effect at all.</p>

<p>“I betrayed it because of you. So you deal with your men yourself!”</p>

<p>The Fist Demon King fought fiercely. He punched, grappled, rolled, jumped, and kicked—raging like a wounded beast.</p>

<p>But there were too many of them. No matter how exceptional his movements were, he was overwhelmed by their sheer numbers.</p>

<p>Blood spurted from Dan Woo-gang’s arms and side. He didn’t have the luxury to check where or how badly he was injured. He frantically swung his fists, dodging swords that flew at him from every direction.</p>

<p>Smack!</p>

<p>At that moment, a flying kick struck the Fist Demon King, sending him crashing into a pile of crates in the courtyard.</p>

<p>It was a vicious strike from Chu Ga-o, who had been waiting for an opportunity.</p>

<p>“Get those gloves off him!”</p>

<p>The Black Path men swarmed around and ripped the gloves off the Fist Demon King. In the process, he bit into the neck of one of them, and blood sprayed everywhere.</p>

<p>Thud! Thud! Thud!</p>

<p>Blows rained down on the Fist Demon King, leaving his face covered in blood.</p>

<p>Chu Ga-o looked down at him.</p>

<p>“I’ve never seen such a stubborn bastard.”</p>

<p>Chu Ga-o clicked his tongue as he glanced at his subordinates. It was at that moment that Dan Woo-gang hurled something from a bottle at him.</p>

<p>Chu Ga-o quickly waved his hand to block it.</p>

<p>Sizzle!</p>

<p>The liquid splashed onto his sleeve, burning it. What was thrown at him was Acid of Bone Dissolution.</p>

<p>Thud! Thud! Thud!</p>

<p>Chu Ga-o, his eyes wide with fury, started stomping on the Fist Demon King. If he hadn’t dodged, his head would have been doused in the acid.</p>

<p>Dan Woo-gang curled up, trying to protect his vital points, but he sensed that this was the end.</p>

<p>‘So this is as far as I go.’</p>

<p>Faced with death, he felt fear creeping in. He also felt a deep sense of injustice and anger at the thought of dying at the hands of someone like Chu Ga-o.</p>

<p>When the beating paused for a moment, the Fist Demon King opened his eyes.</p>

<p>Chu Ga-o was pulling out a dagger.</p>

<p>“You won’t die easily.”</p>

<p>Dan Woo-gang, dazed, looked up at the night sky one last time. He wanted to catch a glimpse of the stars or the moon before dying.</p>

<p>‘Huh?’</p>

<p>Beyond Chu Ga-o’s shoulder, on a branch in the distance, a man was sitting, looking down at him. The Fist Demon King blinked, thinking it might be a hallucination, but when he opened his eyes again, the man was still there, illuminated by the bright full moon.</p>

<p>The man appeared to be a few years older than him.</p>

<p>The Fist Demon King met the man’s gaze. He had never felt fear from looking at another person before, but the coldness in this man’s eyes sent a chill down his spine.</p>

<p>‘Is he the reaper here to take me?’</p>

<p>That thought even crossed his mind.</p>

<p>But the man was not a reaper. One of the Black Path men spotted him by following his gaze.</p>

<p>“Hey! There’s someone over there!”</p>

<p>As all eyes focused on him, the man leapt off the branch effortlessly.</p>

<p>He jumped from quite a height, yet not a single sound was heard as he landed. Both the Black Path men and Dan Woo-gang were stunned by his extraordinary movement technique.</p>

<p>The man walked over slowly and looked at the Fist Demon King. He didn’t even glance at the Black Path men.</p>

<p>He asked the Fist Demon King, “Can you still fight?”</p>

<p>The Fist Demon King nodded and forced himself to stand. His whole body felt like it was breaking apart, and his legs were wobbling under his weight, but he gritted his teeth and kept going.</p>

<p>“I can fight.”</p>

<p>The man then turned his gaze to Chu Ga-o.</p>

<p>“Isn’t it disgraceful to treat a fighter like this?”</p>

<p>Judging by his knowledge of the Fist Demon King being a fighter, he was no mere passerby. It seemed he already understood exactly what was going on.</p>

<p>“Who are you, and where are you from?” Chu Ga-o asked, his nerves on edge. He was worried that a master from the Unorthodox Alliance had shown up because of his meddling.</p>

<p>But the young man’s response was completely unexpected.</p>

<p>“Fight fair and square.”</p>

<p>Whiiiish.</p>

<p>Without any chance to react, a gust of wind generated by the man suppressed Chu Ga-o’s inner power. The technique of subduing an opponent’s inner power with just a flick of a finger was something Chu Ga-o had only ever heard of in tales shared over drinks.</p>

<p>Startled, Chu Ga-o shouted reflexively, “Kill him! Kill this one too!”</p>

<p>But no one dared to charge at the man. Even without the display of skill, there was an undeniable aura about him that commanded respect and fear.</p>

<p>The man gestured for the Black Path men to form a circle around them. As if bewitched, the men arranged themselves in a ring, creating a small arena.</p>

<p>The Fist Demon King, who had barely managed to stand up, clenched his numb fists. He didn’t know who this man was, but he knew that missing this chance would mean his death.</p>

<p>Chu Ga-o also realized that to survive, he had to kill the Fist Demon King. Fortunately, although his inner power had been suppressed, his dagger and sword hadn’t been taken away.</p>

<p>‘If that’s the case, I still have a chance!’</p>

<p>But in fact there was no chance. Chu Ga-o swung his dagger wildly, only to lose his grip when it suddenly flew off his hand, then pulled out his sword and tried to flail it, only to have it snatched away as well.</p>

<p>Ultimately, it came down to a fistfight. And there was no way he could win barehanded against an opponent who had bested him even when he wielded a sword.</p>

<p>Thud! Thwack! Crack! Bam!</p>

<p>Dan Woo-gang’s enraged fists pounded into Chu Ga-o’s body.</p>

<p>“Why! Why do you torment people who are just trying to live their lives?! Why?!”</p>

<p>Chu Ga-o’s jaw and ribs shattered under the blows.</p>

<p>Unable to endure any longer, Chu Ga-o collapsed, panting heavily as he lay on the ground. The Fist Demon King pulled open his shirt, exposing the scar.</p>

<p>“You told me to look at this scar whenever I had stupid thoughts, didn’t you? Well, take a good look yourself before you fucking die.”</p>

<p>Bang! Bang! Bang! Bang!</p>

<p>With the final flurry of punches, Chu Ga-o’s life pitifully ended.</p>

<p>The Fist Demon King, panting heavily, stood up and looked at the man.</p>

<p>At that moment, a sword rose in front of the man. 5</p>

<p>Schwaaa.</p>

<p>The sword split into countless blade auras, forming sword-shaped energies that all shot up into the sky. As the Black Path men stared in awe at the spectacle above them.</p>

<p>Whoosh! Whoosh! Whoosh! Whoosh!</p>

<p>The sword auras hanging in the air rained down like a storm, piercing the heads, faces, and chests of the Black Path men, dropping them all at once.</p>

<p>Not a single Black Path man was left alive.</p>

<p>Hearing the story, Geom Mugeuk exclaimed.</p>

<p>“‘Rain of a Thousand Swords,’ the Soaring Sword Art! So it was father!”</p>

<p>“That’s right. It was the Cult Leader.”</p>

<p>Geom Mugeuk was astonished. He hadn’t known that the person who discovered the Fist Demon King was his own father.</p>

<p>“That was the Cult Leader when he was your age, even before he was named as the successor.”</p>

<p>Hearing that the Cult Leader had saved the Fist Demon King, Geom Mugeuk felt a strange sense of awe.</p>

<p>“Standing amidst all those corpses, the Cult Leader looked at me and said, ‘Why don’t you turn those baby fists into the fists of a real man?’”</p>

<p>“Ah!”</p>

<p>Now, Geom Mugeuk understood where the Fist Demon King’s term “baby hands” originated from.</p>

<p>“So, what did you say?” Geom Mugeuk asked.</p>

<p>“I said no. How could I follow someone I didn’t even know? What if he was an assassin? What if he was the worst villain of our time? I told him, ‘Thank you for saving my life, but no, I’m not going with you.’”</p>

<p>Even in that situation, the Fist Demon King’s refusal was impressive. The young Fist Demon King seemed so full of life and defiance. It was astonishing to think that this vibrant spirit was hidden within the man who now silently oversaw the training of his subordinates every day, seeming stern and unyielding. Who would have imagined that Dan Woo-gang had such a lively youth?</p>

<p>“So, what did my father say to that?”</p>

<p>“He just turned around without a word, with a look that said, ‘Do as you please.’ As I watched his back, I suddenly felt that this wasn’t right. If I didn’t go with him, I’d never escape this damn fighting arena. I had been lucky to survive this time, but I realized I’d eventually end up dying in some similar dirty mess.”</p>

<p>The Fist Demon King recalled that pivotal moment. His destiny had changed because of that brief decision.</p>

<p>“Maybe if the Cult Leader had tried to persuade me, I would have stubbornly refused to the end. Back then, I thought that stubbornness and defiance were virtues. But as I watched him walk away, my body moved on its own. I ran after him, apologizing, saying my mind had changed. And then the Cult Leader looked at me and laughed. You know the one, right? The Cult Leader’s characteristic….”</p>

<p>“That condescending smirk, like he’s looking down on people?” 6</p>

<p>“Yeah, that one.”</p>

<p>“My father truly wears that smirk better than anyone else in the world,” Geom Mugeuk said.</p>

<p>“To be honest, the Cult Leader was impressive that day. He had a different kind of charm compared to you.”</p>

<p>“Am I impressive too?”</p>

<p>The Fist Demon King completely ignored my comment and continued his story.</p>

<p>“The Cult Leader brought me to the Cult without a word and put me into the Eastern Fist Faction. After that, he never came to see me again.”</p>

<p>“That sounds just like my father.”</p>

<p>“I climbed up from the Red Fists to the Black Fists all on my own. I really put in the blood, sweat, and tears back then.”</p>

<p>With his innate sense for martial arts, his talent, and his relentless effort, the Fist Demon King must have attracted everyone’s attention at the time.</p>

<p>“On the day I became part of the Black Fists, the Cult Leader came to see me. It was as if he had been watching me the whole time and showed up exactly on that day. Do you know what he said to me?”</p>

<p>“What did he say?”</p>

<p>Dan Woo-gang’s voice trembled slightly as he recalled that day.</p>

<p>“He said, ‘I will become the Heavenly Demon, so you become my Fist Demon King.’”</p>

<p>The bond between the two wasn’t just because they were obsessed with martial arts. It was because of this hidden past they shared.</p>

<p>Geom Mugeuk, shamelessly mimicking his father, said, “Then I will become the Heavenly Demon, so—”</p>

<p>“It’s too late. I’m already the Fist Demon King”, Dan Woo-gang interjected.</p>

<p>“Ah! Right, that’s something I should be saying to Cheon So-hee. Give me a moment; I’ll find something that suits us better”, Geom Mugeuk replied with a smirk.</p>

<p>Dan Woo-gang watched Geom Mugeuk intently.</p>

<p>For a brief moment, the image of young, arrogant Geom Woojin overlapped with Geom Mugeuk’s joking figure.</p>

<p>Two similar yet different people. If Geom Mugeuk was light, then Geom Woojin was darkness. If one felt so light he could float away, the other felt so heavy he seemed destined to sink forever. 7</p>

<p>But the Fist Demon King felt it again—the realization that light and darkness were not so different. They were bright yet dark, and dark yet bright.</p>

<p>“The Cult Leader took me away from this place, yet you were the one who brought me back here.”</p>

<p>The Fist Demon King had now met two young successors of the Cult, bound by blood, in this very place. He felt it was a sign of some grand destiny.</p>

<p>Then, Geom Mugeuk looked calmly at Dan Woo-gang and spoke with quiet resolve.</p>

<p>“I will be your disciple. Please become my master!”</p>

<p>1 : You didn’t plan to in the first place anyways, so might as well trash talk you properly.</p>

<p>2 : This kid had guts, I think old man Heavens liked him and sent him help. Or, following his rule, Dan Woo-gang’s struggles were met with adequate compensation.</p>

<p>3 : A good resolve. Respect.</p>

<p>4 : Run wild, be vicious, forget honor, the one who survive until the end was right by rule of the strongest. Plus, it’s not like trash like them can complain about fairness.</p>

<p>5 : So not the previous Fist Demon King. Maybe Geom Woojin ?</p>

<p>6 : Even young, he was still the Cult Leader XDXDXD</p>

<p>7 : Two sides of the same coin, the past, looking down at the cold abyss of broken dreams and memories, and the future, looking up at the bright sky full of hope and freedom.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Translator: FenrirTL Editor/Quality Checker: Saphartlantis Murim Term Consultant: Kopke]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Chapter 198: Do You Think That’s Going to Be Easy</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2025/11/09/chapter-198.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Chapter 198: Do You Think That’s Going to Be Easy" /><published>2025-11-09T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-11-09T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2025/11/09/chapter-198</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2025/11/09/chapter-198.html"><![CDATA[<p>Translator: FenrirTL
Editor/Quality Checker: Saphartlantis, Mani
Murim Term Consultant: Kopke</p>

<p>========================</p>

<p>&lt; Chapter 198: Do You Think That’s Going to Be Easy? &gt;</p>

<p>The usual words from the Fist Demon King didn’t come this time.</p>

<p>It was a good attempt.</p>

<p>Had my effort finally paid off? Or was he simply deciding not to bring it up anymore?</p>

<p>Dan Woo-gang silently turned his gaze towards the arena. Two men were fighting fiercely, blood spraying everywhere. And the crowd was going wild for them.</p>

<p>“This place will look exactly the same even after decades have passed.”</p>

<p>“My son might come here someday with you when you’re old and gray.”</p>

<p>The Fist Demon King looked at me, startled.</p>

<p>“Why do you look so surprised?”</p>

<p>“Are you thinking of getting married?”</p>

<p>“If I meet someone good, maybe.”</p>

<p>Of course, I had no intention of getting married, but I gave the typical answer. 1</p>

<p>The Fist Demon King spoke firmly.</p>

<p>“I’d advise against it unless it’s someone you truly care about.”</p>

<p>He often talked about his younger days, mentioning that he had decided long ago never to have a family or friends, so I figured that’s why he gave such advice. But there was another reason behind it.</p>

<p>“Even for someone as exceptional as you, look at how difficult it is to avoid bloody conflicts over succession. Do you think your children could manage like you? It’s a burden too great for ordinary people.”</p>

<p>It was both a compliment to me and a concern for the future. Most importantly, it was based on the assumption that I might become the Heavenly Demon.</p>

<p>“I’ll consider it carefully.”</p>

<p>“Come to think of it, you did mention ending the Heavenly Demon bloodline ‘siblings killings’.”</p>

<p>“It doesn’t matter. It’s something that happens after I return. For now I’m on vacation.”</p>

<p>Hearing my words, the Fist Demon King had a look that said he truly believed I might genuinely be that carefree about it.</p>

<p>“Let’s head out.”</p>

<p>“Yes.”</p>

<p>At the exit, Dan Woo-gang took one last look at the arena. Would he ever visit this place again in his lifetime? The future was uncertain, but he seemed to be viewing it as a place he’d never return to. His eyes, filled with complex emotions, scanned the surroundings slowly. But once he turned away, he walked out with brisk steps.</p>

<p>After leaving the arena, we walked without a set destination. The Fist Demon King didn’t ask where we were going next. I, too, followed the path without any particular thought, as if having no plan was the plan.</p>

<p>“Have you ever been lost?”</p>

<p>“Never.”</p>

<p>“Neither have I.”</p>

<p>Perhaps that’s why this aimless wandering felt so valuable and meaningful.</p>

<p>Neither of us had ever lived so unplanned. The joy of losing your way in life was something we could never have imagined.</p>

<p>“By the way, I lost the bet. I admit it.”</p>

<p>“No, I lost this one.”</p>

<p>It was unexpected. Even though he had said it was fine, I thought he wouldn’t feel too great about witnessing match-fixing.</p>

<p>“It’s been a while since I had this much fun. It reminded me of the old days.”</p>

<p>Was this what he wanted to convey? That he showed me what kind of person he truly was.</p>

<p>“So, our pride match is tied at one-to-one.”</p>

<p>“We must settle this.”</p>

<p>“Of course.”</p>

<p>Then, the Fist Demon King spoke up.</p>

<p>“Before that, there’s a place I want to visit.”</p>

<p>For the first time, Dan Woo-gang expressed a desire to go somewhere.</p>

<p>“I’d go to hell with you, Fist Demon King!”</p>

<p>“The place we’re going to isn’t that hot. In fact, you’ll need to bring a thick coat.”</p>

<p>Leaving behind the arena filled with the Fist Demon King’s old memories, we started walking, following the lingering sunset.</p>

<hr />

<p>After a long journey, the Fist Demon King and I stood together at the peak of the snowy mountain.</p>

<p>Whooooosh.</p>

<p>The wind, carrying snow, whipped up the snow around us and sent it swirling into the air.</p>

<p>“Why did you want to come here?”</p>

<p>The place Dan Woo-gang had wanted to visit was this snowy mountain.</p>

<p>“This is where the previous Fist Demon King chose me as his successor.”</p>

<p>“Oh, is that so?”</p>

<p>It was something I hadn’t known.</p>

<p>“In truth, my master and I didn’t get along well. When he was choosing his final successor, he wanted to pick someone else. That guy wasn’t as skilled as me in martial arts, but he was much more agreeable with the master. Do you know why the master ended up choosing me?”</p>

<p>“Was it because of my father?”</p>

<p>“That’s right, because of the Cult Leader.”</p>

<p>When the young Fist Demon King was first placed in the Eastern Fist Faction, my father wasn’t the Cult Leader. However, by the time Dan Woo-gang officially took over the position of the Demon Supreme, my father had risen to the seat of the Heavenly Demon.</p>

<p>The previous Fist Demon King couldn’t ignore the fact that my father had become the Heavenly Demon.</p>

<p>“I became the Fist Demon King because of your father.”</p>

<p>“Isn’t that an even greater honor for you?”</p>

<p>“An honor, you say?”</p>

<p>“My father’s eye for people was better than the previous Fist Demon King’s. My father chose a young fighter brawling in an arena without a shred of inner power. That fighter fought his way up from the Red Fists to the Black Fists, and ultimately became the Fist Demon King. Trust in my father’s judgment when it comes to people.”</p>

<p>“There was a time when I was confident. Who else but me would become the Fist Demon King? But now, I’m not so sure. Was the Cult Leader’s judgment truly correct?”</p>

<p>“If that decision had been wrong, the other Demon Supremes wouldn’t consider you the most difficult Demon Supreme to face. Anyone can see that you’re the one who belongs in that position, Fist Demon King.”</p>

<p>Dan Woo-gang silently gazed at the snowy landscape. It was a breathtaking view, one that could only be experienced from this peak, standing tall in an entirely white world.</p>

<p>I admired the Fist Demon King for his introspection. Without such self-reflection, he would have become a stubborn old man, fossilized in his ways. Because he could look within himself, I believed that Dan Woo-gang could bring down the cliff.</p>

<p>I shared my honest feelings with him.</p>

<p>“At first, I was curious about who you were, Fist Demon King. Then, I became inspired by your goal of breaking down the cliff, and I wanted to break it down myself. Now, I like your true self even more.”</p>

<p>“My true self?”</p>

<p>“I think your true self is the young man who fought against the dark forces. When we return, I’d like to gather all the Iron Fists and tell them that story. ‘Hey! This is who your Fist Demon King truly is!’”</p>

<p>“Did you say such flattering words to the other Demon Supremes too?”</p>

<p>“It wasn’t flattery; I just spoke honestly. I said things that others wouldn’t say because of their positions as Demon Supremes. Of course, I admit I did try to flatter to some extent. I wanted to be seen in a good light, and I wanted to get closer to them. But I never made anything up. I said the kind of things I’d like someone to say about my life one day.” 2</p>

<p>Then, I added while looking at the Fist Demon King.</p>

<p>“But you rarely hear such things, don’t you?”</p>

<p>Even after teaching hundreds, even in a place where tens of thousands of followers come and go.</p>

<p>“You don’t hear such words often, do you?”</p>

<p>Will there be anyone who will say such things about me later? I did all this, but…</p>

<p>Dan Woo-gang silently stared at me. After a long gaze, he turned and looked across the distant mountain again.</p>

<p>“What do you plan to do if you become the Heavenly Demon? Is your dream to unite the martial world under one rule?”</p>

<p>“It’s the opposite.”</p>

<p>“The opposite?”</p>

<p>“I’ll prevent anyone from uniting the martial world, even if it’s my father.” 3</p>

<p>The Fist Demon King’s eyes sparkled.</p>

<p>“You knew, didn’t you?”</p>

<p>That meant the Fist Demon King knew as well.</p>

<p>“I know that my father dreams of uniting the martial world under his rule.”</p>

<p>“Right, someone as smart as you wouldn’t have missed that.”</p>

<p>“What do you think, Fist Demon King?”</p>

<p>“I will follow your father’s wishes. If he orders a war and commands me to kill everyone, I’ll do so without hesitation. No matter who they are.”</p>

<p>Now, it was clear. Dan Woo-gang was my father’s right-hand man. So, was the Blood Heaven Blade Demon his left hand? The elixir that Gu Cheonpa gave me was from my father, according to him.</p>

<p>“I will stop both my father and you, Fist Demon King.”</p>

<p>After that, we stood there in silence for a long time.</p>

<p>Whoooosh.</p>

<p>When the blowing snowstorm brushed past us, the Fist Demon King’s resolution was carried on the wind.</p>

<p>“Mugeuk, I will take you as my first disciple.” 4</p>

<p>I was taken aback. While becoming his disciple had been my goal, I hadn’t expected it to happen here, like this. And it was at a moment when I had just confirmed our conflicting views on uniting the martial world.</p>

<p>His large, broad figure turned toward me. I had grown accustomed to his fearsome face, but today, his eyes were different. With a deep and earnest gaze, the Fist Demon King spoke.</p>

<p>“I will be your master. Become my disciple.”</p>

<p>At that moment, I felt overwhelmed. A surge of joy filled me. I had finally succeeded in moving this man’s heart. It wasn’t just about gaining the Demon Supreme known as the Fist Demon King or learning his martial arts. I was simply overjoyed that this person would be my master.</p>

<p>“Wooaahhh!”</p>

<p>I was so happy that I leapt on the spot, like a puppy excited by the snow, expressing my joy without restraint.</p>

<p>Seeing my genuine delight, Dan Woo-gang’s expression softened. It was surprising to see such gentleness on that usually terrifying face.</p>

<p>I was so thrilled that I executed the First Fist. I aimed it at the empty sky, mindful of the potential for an avalanche. Then, I swiftly followed it up with the Second Fist. 5</p>

<p>“Thank you. Thank you so much.”</p>

<p>Right then and there, I performed the nine-bow salute.</p>

<p>“Disciple Geom Mugeuk formally greets Master. Please guide this foolish disciple with your great and profound teachings.”</p>

<p>The Fist Demon King’s large hand rested on my shoulder. With his rough and thick hand, he lightly patted my shoulder. It was the first time I felt such a gentle touch from him.</p>

<p>“Rise.”</p>

<p>I stood up from my bow.</p>

<p>“Master.”</p>

<p>The Fist Demon King was the first person in both lives that I wanted to have as my master. He was someone who fully deserved it.</p>

<p>“Disciple.”</p>

<p>It seemed Dan Woo-gang didn’t entirely dislike having his first disciple.</p>

<p>“From now on, I will teach you the entire Thunderous Asura Fist.”</p>

<p>The Fist Demon King didn’t delay in passing down his martial arts. He didn’t ask for anything in return for teaching me. That was the kind of man he was.</p>

<p>At the summit of the snowy mountain, the Fist Demon King began the martial arts transmission of the Thunderous Asura Fist, from the Third Technique to the Sixth Technique.</p>

<p>The Third Technique: Heavenly Strike Asura.</p>

<p>It was the heaviest punch among the Fist Demon King’s fists. It didn’t strike distant enemies like the Black Cloud Asura, nor did it deliver fast attacks like the Myriad Winds Asura. It was a direct strike with the fist, and the power contained in each blow was an incredible martial skill.</p>

<p>The Fourth Technique: Iron Leg Asura.</p>

<p>The Thunderous Asura Fist did not consist solely of techniques that used punches. There were also techniques that shattered opponents with powerful kicks. The moves themselves were flashy and impressive, and I was sure that whenever Iron Leg Asura was unleashed, it would be met with admiration.</p>

<p>The Fifth Technique: Diamond Asura.</p>

<p>This technique temporarily transformed the body to be as hard as steel, providing protection. Although it consumed a tremendous amount of internal energy, it was a technique that could save one’s life in a critical moment.</p>

<p>There was hope that if the Fifth Technique were used in conjunction with the Heavenly Demon Body Protection Technique, it might momentarily achieve the effect of Invincible Vajra.</p>

<p>And finally, the Sixth Technique: Yama’s Thunder Asura.</p>

<p>The last technique of the Thunderous Asura Fist. Named for the thunderbolt struck by the King of the Underworld, it was the ultimate move that unleashed all the internal energy in a single strike. It was a technique capable of collapsing a cliff, but if this move failed, it would mean certain death against the opponent.</p>

<p>Only a formidable enemy would necessitate the use of the final sixth technique. If it failed, I would have to face him without a shred of internal energy left.</p>

<p>For seven days at the summit of the snowy mountain, I was taught the Thunderous Asura Fist, from the First Technique to the last, meticulously learning each one again.</p>

<p>Throughout this process, I also received the various insights into martial arts that the Fist Demon King had realized over his lifetime. Once he decided to take me as his disciple, he gave without holding back. I suppose I was charmed by this straightforward nature as well.</p>

<p>Now, all that remains is for me to train diligently and achieve greatness.</p>

<p>Even if I lose my sword in future battles, it won’t present an opportunity for my opponent. Instead, that moment will be my chance to strike a careless enemy with a single blow.</p>

<p>“When we return to the Cult, I plan to make two announcements. First, that I have accepted you as my disciple. Second, that the Eastern Fist Faction officially supports the Eldest Young Master.”</p>

<p>It was as expected. This announcement would surely stir up quite a commotion within the Cult. How would the other Demon Supremes or my brother react? And what about my father?</p>

<p>“They’ll all see me as a greedy man with a foot in both your and Geom Muyang’s camps.”</p>

<p>“So what if they do? If that’s how Master chooses to live, then so be it. If they’re jealous, they can try doing the same. Not that it’ll be easy, you cowards!” I retorted playfully.</p>

<p>Dan Woo-gang laughed. I could feel that his laughter towards me had become much more relaxed.</p>

<p>“Let’s go down now, disciple.”</p>

<p>“Yes, Master.”</p>

<p>I walked down the snowy mountain with the Fist Demon King, leaving footprints on the untouched snow. Though both of us had long mastered the level of “stepping on snow without leaving a trace”, we deliberately pressed our footprints deeply into the snow as we descended.</p>

<p>If I could, I would have liked to leave footprints on the stone ground and set up a sign next to them:</p>

<p><em>The path down the mountain where the Fist Demon King and Geom Mugeuk walked as master and disciple.</em></p>

<p>After descending the mountain, we naturally set our course towards the Cult.</p>

<p>Before departing, we stopped by the Swallow Tail Inn near the snowy mountain to check if there were any messages for me.</p>

<p>“Ah! Master, there’s somewhere I need to stop by before we go.”</p>

<p>“Where?”</p>

<p>“I received a message from my people asking to meet me.”</p>

<p>Gowol and Jeong Dae, who were out in the Central Plains establishing an information network, had sent me a message requesting a meeting.</p>

<p>“So what? Are you going to abandon me?”</p>

<p>“Abandon you?”</p>

<p>“Isn’t that the same as telling me to go back alone? Now that you’ve learned all the martial arts, you’re saying you’re done with me. Isn’t that it? Ah! That’s why they say you shouldn’t give everything all at once.” 6</p>

<p>I didn’t expect such words from the Fist Demon King, so I burst into laughter.</p>

<p>“Well, if you come with me, who knows when we’ll be able to return.”</p>

<p>Gowol wouldn’t have called me for something trivial.</p>

<p>“Will your Iron Fist classes be alright?”</p>

<p>He had already been absent for quite a few days, so I was considerate, thinking that he might be concerned.</p>

<p>“What’s there to worry about? I have a disciple now.”</p>

<p>“You’ve quickly learned how to say things that make people feel good.”</p>

<p>The Fist Demon King strode ahead and said,</p>

<p>“Well, whose master do you think I am?” 7</p>

<p>1 : It’s “I had no intention of getting married”…. yet ^^</p>

<p>2 : It’s true, he technically never lied. He just arranged his words according to the listener.</p>

<p>3 : Yeah, that world was hollow and rotten.</p>

<p>4 : Yaaayy !!!! Friendship !!!!</p>

<p>5 : Victory pose ^^</p>

<p>6 : Gu Cheonpa, release this body !!!</p>

<p>7 : The corruption was fast XDXDXD But yeah, it’s nice to see him relax ^^</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Translator: FenrirTL Editor/Quality Checker: Saphartlantis, Mani Murim Term Consultant: Kopke]]></summary></entry></feed>